Guide to the New Almaden Mine (Calif.) Collection, 1845-1973
Department of Special Collections
- SERIES VII: MAPS AND PLANS
  - HARRY, SANTA MARIANA, VELASCO, VICTORIA
    - Velasco to Theatre, with additions, old #219V, 1967; 8.5x11 40 (Folder 35-3)
      Ingle
    - Day Tunnel, cross sections, ca. 1969; 22x24 50 (Folder 35-4)
      Atwood
    - Victoria Shaft, 800-950, transport to Good Friday, old #22, 13.5x36 (Folder 35-5)
    - Giant Powder to Victoria, South Saint George, Plate 18, old #180, Apr/May; 23x31 (Folder 35-6)
    - Shaft Map, Yellow Kid Tunnel, color, 11.25x12 (Folder 35-7)
    - Shaft Map, Yellow Kid Tunnel, color, 11.25x12 (Folder 35-8)
    - Shaft Map, Yellow Kid Tunnel, color, 11.25x12 (Folder 35-9)
    - Shaft Map, Good Friday, Oregon, 18x24 (Folder 35-10)
    - Profile and surface of Day Tunnel, old #109, 18x26 200 (Folder 35-11)
    - Robles Tunnel, Upper Velasco, Lower Velasco, Bush Tunnel, 14x18 40/20 (Folder 35-12)
    - Victoria, Oregon, West Drift, shaft map, 18x24 (Folder 35-13)
    - Great Powder Labor, Ponce Labor, layout map, 18x24 (Folder 35-14)
  - CORA BLANCA
    - C. Faull, Los Angeles Tunnels, flat section 30, pencil, old #60, 1872; 8.5x24 30 (Folder 35-15)
    - Deep Gulch, Cora Blanca, some topographical notes, old #61, 15x28 200 (Folder 36-1)
    - Cora Blanca, Profile and Grey Shaft, old #62, 22x37 (Folder 36-2)
    - Cora Blanca, Vertical section, North and South through Shaft, old #66, 1874; 20x25 40 (Folder 36-3)
    - Cora Blanca, 500, with notes by CNS, verso: Hacienda Bridge, pencil, old #69, 1943; 18.5x27.5 (Folder 36-4)
      CNS, Hoffman
    - Cora Blanca, Grey shaft, Deep Gulch, plate XXX, old #71, 32x42 (Folder 36-5)
    - Plan of the Underground works of the Quicksilver Mining Company, 1880; 24.5x37 80 (Folder 36-6)
    - Open cut progress map of benches, office copy with color and 480 added, old #86, 1942; 17x22 40 (Folder 36-7)
      Schuette
    - Open cut progress map of benches, office copy with color, old #86, 1942; 17x22 40 (Folder 36-8)
    - Open cut benches, Cora Blanca and Los Angeles, old #88, 1942; 18.5x19.5 40 (Folder 36-9)
    - Cora Blanca, Los Angeles, Deep Gulch Tunnel Past Grey, recto and verso, old #91, 1879; 18x18 80 (Folder 36-10)
      PL
    - Cora Blanca, North/South and East/West cross sections, old #94, 1879; 22.5x26.5 80 (Folder 36-11)
      PL?
    - Cora Blanca, 600, old #95B, 24x26 (Folder 36-12)
    - Cora Blanca, 700-800, old #95C, 25x23.5 (Folder 36-13)
    - Cora Blanca, upper levels, old 95D, 24x25 (Folder 36-14)
    - Cora Blanca, 500, old #95E, 24x25.5 (Folder 36-15)
    - Cora Blanca, Mine Hill, San Francisco, old #238, 31.5x27.5 200 (Folder 37-1)
    - Hacienda Furnace Yard, underground works, shafts 1-3, furnace #8, old #333, 23x31 (Folder 37-2)
      Jennings?
    - Cora Blanca, preliminary underground, Grey Shaft shown, 1940; 36x36 60 (Folder 37-3)
    - Cora Blanca, open cut progress map, 1940; 17x22 40 (Folder 37-4)
    - Cora Blanca, color, matted, fragment, 45x56 (Folder 37-5)
    - Cora Blanca, composite, see Wisser, 1941, ca.1941; 22x36 40 (Folder 37-6)
    - Working map of the Cora Blanca Mine, 1876; 18x24 20 (Folder 37-7)
    - Cora Blanca Shaft, color, old #93, 9.5x17.75 (Folder 37-8)
    - Faull Tunnel, Cora Blanca Shaft, Shaft Map, 18x24 (Folder 37-9)
  - SAN FRANCISCO
    - San Francisco, vertical cross section, 300 down, NE corner of shaft, old #403, 23x41 40 (Folder 37-10)
      Wilkinson
    - San Francisco, Branch tunnel, brittle, old #405, 1890; 22x48 20 (Folder 37-11)
    - San Francisco, Warren Stope, 800, available workings, old #419, 1943; 21.5x27.5 40 (Folder 37-12)
      United States Geological Association
    - San Francisco, San Cristobal, old #422, 1959; 23x36 150 (Folder 37-13)
      J.T.H., Whitaker?
    - San Francisco, 400-600, brittle, old #423, 22x29 40 (Folder 37-14)
    - San Francisco, connection with Garfield Shaft and Santa Clara drift, old #426, 1882; 16.75x42 40/10 (Folder 37-15)
    - San Francisco, 320 and El Italiano stope, old #427, 20x25 20 (Folder 38-1)
    - San Francisco, Don Ricardo and Faull, old #428, 21x22 (Folder 38-2)
    - San Francisco, Washington #1 chute workings, old #429, 1942; 8.5x18 40 (Folder 38-3)
    - San Francisco, 300 section near shaft, survey in San Francisco branch open cut tunnel, pencil, old #431, ca. 1874; 15x17 (Folder 38-4)
    - San Cristobal Mine, horizontal and vertical, Hank's stope, old #439, 1966; 12x12.5 20 (Folder 38-5)
    - San Francisco shaft, south side hill, old #439 (Folder 38-6)
    - San Cristobal, horizontal and 300, old #442, 20x24 40 (Folder 38-7)
    - San Cristobal, horizontal and vertical, Hank's stope, old #442C, 1966; 12.5x12.5 20 (Folder 38-8)
    - Overlays, 2100-2300, 3 pieces, Washington?, 18.5x18.5 (Folder 38-9)
    - Washington 900, 23x24 (Folder 38-10)
    - San Cristobal, 1968; 18x24 50 (Folder 38-11)
    - San Francisco, Faull stopes to Don Ricardo, 1968; 12x24 50? (Folder 38-12)
    - Upper New World stopes and connected workings, 1944; 23x24 50 (Folder 38-13)
    - San Cristobal Tunnel and 300 workings, 1944; 23x24 50 (Folder 38-14)
    - San Francisco stopes, Washington, 400 level, 1944; 23x24 50 (Folder 38-15)
    - Washington Shaft Area from old maps, see 1881 survey reports, 20x36 40? (Folder 39-1)
    - Washington Shaft Area from old maps, sheets 1, 3-5, old #408, 1967; 15x18 40 (Folder 39-2)
    - San Cristobal, Mine sheets 1-5, 1967; 15x18 40 (Folder 39-3)
    - San Francisco Shaft, San Cristobal Levels, 18 x 23.75 40 (Folder 39-4)
    - San Cristobal, old #440, 1966; 9x14.5 40 (Folder 39-5)
      H.C. Ingle, Jr.
    - San Cristobal, old #440, 1966; 10.5x14 40 (Folder 39-6)
      H. C. Ingle, Jr.
    - Shaft Map, San Francisco Tunnel?, 18x24 (Folder 39-7)
    - Washington shaft, San Cristobal tunnel, 18x24 (Folder 39-8)
  - SAN PEDRO, ALMADEN
    - Vertical section, Great Eastern to 700, old #116, 11.75x19 (Folder 39-9)
      White?
    - Velasco, Great Eastern, Mobley Raise Sections, old #209, 1961; 12x14 (Folder 39-10)
      E. Bailey
    - Great Eastern Sink?, old #219E, 14x18 (Folder 39-11)
      J. White?
    - Great Eastern and North Cross cut, old #219M, 1959; 8.5x11 40 (Folder 39-12)
      Stager, Bailey
    - San Pedro, San Ramon, see also 450-452, old #478, 22.5x30 (Folder 39-13)
    - Profile, plan, San Pedro, old #479, 1875; 27x27 20 (Folder 39-14)
    - San Pedro, 1875, blueprint, see 240, fragment, old #480, 1882; 8.5x22 (Folder 39-15)
    - San Pedro, Delores and level above, pencil, old #481, 1966; 8.5x11 40 (Folder 40-1)
    - San Pedro, Delores and level above, pencil, old #482, 1966; 12.5x22 40 (Folder 40-2)
    - San Pedro, cross section, old #483, 1966?; 5x7 100 (Folder 40-3)
    - San Pedro, see 481, old #485, 1966; 8.5x11 40 (Folder 40-4)
    - Dolores Taranga holing point from top of D-4 raise, 1969; 16x18 20 (Folder 40-5)
      JOC
    - San Pedro?, unidentified, 1969; 12x21 20 (Folder 40-6)
    - San Pedro?, projected workings, around 1525, ca1969; 12x24 20 (Folder 40-7)
    - San Pedro?, workings, part 1, 1970; 12x21 20 (Folder 40-8)
      Harrington
    - San Pedro?, workings, part 2, 1970; 10x21 20 (Folder 40-9)
    - San Pedro, workings, 1969; 15x21 50 (Folder 40-10)
    - D-4 and D-5 raise, Almaden, 1969; 18.75x24 (Folder 40-11)
    - San Pedro workings, 1969; 15x21 50 (Folder 40-12)
    - San Pedro, open pit assay samples, 1969; 13x19 20 (Folder 40-13)
    - Dolores Taranga 1462, floor level, rat damage, 1968; 16x24 50 (Folder 40-14)
    - San Pedro, 1515, DT 1461.77, survey coordinates, geology?, 1969; 25x30 50 (Folder 40-15)
    - Almaden, April workings, 1969; 24x27 20 (Folder 41-1)
    - Almaden, April workings, 1969; 24x31 20 (Folder 41-2)
    - D-4 raise, Dolores Taranga, 1969; 11x18 20 (Folder 41-3)
    - Almaden 600, New Idria, 1969; 24x42 50 (Folder 41-4)
      New Idria Mining and Chemical Co.
    - Subsurface contour map, San Pedro, 24x38.5 50 (Folder 41-5)
    - Almaden Shaft and April Tunnel area, 1968; 24x42 50 (Folder 41-6)
    - San Pedro, open pit, 1969; 24x27 20 (Folder 41-7)
  - NORTH RANDOL
    - Randol, Santa Isabel, cross section to 2000 level, old #3, 26x38 (Folder 41-8)
    - Randol, Santa Isabel, cross section to 2100 level, old #4, 27x40.5 (Folder 41-9)
    - Randol, Santa Isabel, cross section North and South, Becker/United States Geological Survey folio, old #5, 1888; 17x22 150 (Folder 41-10)
      Becker
    - Randol, Santa Isabel, cross section East and West, Becker/ United States Geological Survey folio to 2100 level, old #6, 1885; 17x22 150 (Folder 41-11)
      Reade, Becker
    - Randol, Santa Isabel, cross section East and West to 1800 level, blue print, old #7, 1880; 25x39 80 (Folder 41-12)
    - Randol, Santa Isabel, cross section East and West to 1800 level, blue print, old #7, 1880; 25x39 80 (Folder 41-13)
    - Randol, Santa Isabel, cross section East and West to 1800 level, blue print, old #8, 1880; 28.5x42.5 80 (Folder 41-14)
    - Randol, Santa Isabel, North and South vertical section, old #9, 1880; 28.5x42.5 80 (Folder 41-15)
    - Randol, Santa Isabel, blueprint, old #9, 1880; 25x36.5 80 (Folder 42-1)
    - Randol, Santa Isabel, tunnel profile with pencil notes, old #21, 1890; 12x41 20 (Folder 42-2)
      RCB
    - Randol, Santa Isabel, tunnel mouth, plan for planilla, old #22, ca.1878; 23.5x27 10 (Folder 42-3)
    - Randol, Santa Isabel, tunnel section profile to shaft, old #23, 13.25x24 80 (Folder 42-4)
    - Randol, Santa Isabel, Santa Isabel and stopes to Mine Hill, old #25, 11x12 200 (Folder 42-5)
    - Day Tunnel plan to Randol, old #261, 18x23 80 (Folder 42-6)
      White
    - Randol 1500 level, old #35, 32x39 40 (Folder 42-7)
    - Santa Isabel 2200 level, old #36, 17x38.5 40 (Folder 42-8)
    - Randol 1600 level, old #40, 23.5x38.5 40 (Folder 42-9)
    - Randol Hanging Walls (see 47) old #50, 17.5x25 100 (Folder 42-10)
    - Randol, West vertical section, Cornish drift to 900, old #105, 1873; 30x31.5 60 (Folder 42-11)
    - North Randol 1000 to O'Brion, tracing of old map?, 17x33 (Folder 42-12)
    - North Randol 900 level, 12x13 (Folder 42-13)
    - Shaft map, Victoria and North Randol, 14x25.5 (Folder 42-14)
    - Pruyn drift plan, workings, 1870; 18x24 20 (Folder 42-15)
      Leconte
  - SOUTH RANDOL
    - South Randol, Hanging Walls, 587-2033 levels, old #11, 1885; 32x42.5 (Folder 43-1)
      Reade
    - South Randol, Santa Isabel, Church Shaft, cross section, lower 1600-2450, old #12, 13.5x24 150 (Folder 43-2)
    - Santa Isabel, Horizontal section, 1400 level, dates of work, old #13, 1888; 26.5x29.5 (Folder 43-3)
    - Santa Isabel, 1050-1600-2300 levels, geology, Buena Vista, old #19, 1877; 14x14 40 (Folder 43-4)
      Foote
    - Santa Isabel, 1900 level, old #44, 30x38 40 (Folder 43-5)
    - Randol, hanging walls, drifts run on vein of no. production, old #47, 27x42.5 80 (Folder 43-6)
    - Randol, reduction, 7.5x10 400 (Folder 43-7)
    - Santa Isabel, Randol 1700 level, old #49, 24.5x38.5 40 (Folder 43-8)
    - Randol, Santa Rita West to 1700, see 24A, blueprint, old #52, 1885; 22x34 40 (Folder 43-9)
    - Randol, Santa Rita West to 1700, see 24A, blueprint, old #52, 1885; 22x34 40 (Folder 43-10)
    - April Tunnel, 1969; 13x17 20 (Folder 43-11)
    - April Tunnel Section, 1969; 16x30.5 200 (Folder 43-12)
    - NAE-2, Proposed April Tunnel drift 1245, 1968; 24x30 50 (Folder 43-13)
    - NAE-8, Approximate section line along proposed haul road, April Tunnel, 1968; 24x26 50 (Folder 43-14)
    - April Tunnel Benches, 1969; 15x18 50 (Folder 43-15)
    - April Tunnel washout profile, 1969; 24x27 50 (Folder 44-1)
    - April Tunnel Area, survey co-ordinates?, 1969; 24x32 20 (Folder 44-2)
    - NAE-7, April Tunnel turn about, 1969; 21x24 20 (Folder 44-3)
    - NAE-6, April Tunnel proposed haulage road, 1969; 21x24 20 (Folder 44-4)
    - April Tunnel, elevations, pencil, 1969; 18.5x24 20 (Folder 44-5)
    - April Tunnel, haulage road, 1969; 24x25 20 (Folder 44-6)
    - April Tunnel, turn about, 1969; 20.5x24 20 (Folder 44-7)
    - Shaft Map, Santa Isabel, 14x25.5 (Folder 44-8)
    - Randol Shaft, tagboard with photographs pasted on, 22x28 (Folder 44-9)
    - RRB shaft, tagboard with photographs pasted on, 22x28 50 (Folder 44-10)
    - Shaft Map, Santa Isabel, Drain Tunnel, 18x24 (Folder 44-11)
    - Shaft Map, Buena Vista shaft, 18x24 (Folder 44-12)
    - Shaft Map, Randol Tunnel, 18x24 20 (Folder 44-13)
    - Shaft Map, Santa Isabel Shaft, date drilled, and how far, 18x24 (Folder 44-14)
    - Shaft Map, Randol Shaft, color, 18x24 (Folder 44-15)
    - Shaft Map, Randol Tunnel, color, 18x24 (Folder 45-1)
    - Randol Shaft, color, 12x15.5 20 (Folder 45-2)
  - AMERICA
    - Plan of the underground works, America, San Pedro, San Mateo, Providence, Enriquita, old #240A, 1889; 25x39 80 (Folder 45-3)
    - America Shaft, upper tunnel to 1400, plate 16, old #510, 1888; 23x28 40 (Folder 45-4)
    - America, upper and lower tunnels, plate 21, old #511, 1888; 21x31 40 (Folder 45-5)
    - America, upper and lower tunnels and elevations, old #512, ca. 1868; 18x26 40 (Folder 45-6)
    - America, upper and lower tunnels, old #513, 18x30 30 (Folder 45-7)
      Hawley
    - America, upper and lower tunnels, San Pedro, Hacienda Tunnel on verso, old #514, ca. 1883; 16.5x35 80 (Folder 45-8)
    - New Lower America 675, old #515, 1966; 18x24 200 (Folder 45-9)
      Schneider
    - America, workings, new 650 cross-cut, see 520, 522, old #519, 1966; 37x42 40 (Folder 45-10)
    - America, up to date, color, old #520, 1966; 37x42 40 (Folder 45-11)
    - America, up to date, color, old #521, 1968; 10x13 100 (Folder 45-12)
    - America, small photos, see 523, old #521b, 1968; 6x7.25 200 (Folder 45-13)
    - America, up to date, 650 new tunnel, same as 520, old #522, 1966; 37x42 40 (Folder 45-14)
    - America, 1940 plan, original, old #523, 1962; 23x31 40 (Folder 45-15)
      Frederick
    - America, 1940 plan, positive blueprint, old #523, 1962; 23x31 40 (Folder 46-1)
    - Old Underground workings, see 520, positive blueprint, 1966; 37x42 40 (Folder 46-2)
      Ingle, United States Geological Survey
    - America workings, color, matted, 16x18 40 (Folder 46-3)
    - America Shaft, cross section, color, 1968; 23x24 (Folder 46-4)
      Botts
    - America, 700 level, 1968; 24x42 50 (Folder 46-5)
    - America, 600 level, 1968; 24x42 50 (Folder 46-6)
    - America, 500 level, 1968; 24x42 50 (Folder 46-7)
    - America shaft, vertical cross section E. W., 1969; 18x24 50 (Folder 46-8)
      K. Harrington
  - PROVIDENCE-ENRIQUITA
    - Plan of the underground works of the Quicksilver Mining Company, Providence-Enriquita, America, San Pedro, San Mateo, old # 240B, 1889; 25x39 80 (Folder 46-9)
    - Plan of the underground works of the Quicksilver Mining Company, Providence-Enriquita, America, San Pedro, San Mateo, old # 240C, 1889; 25x39 80 (Folder 46-10)
    - Grade Eldredge Tunnel, notes attached, old #530, 1924; 18x23 (Folder 46-11)
      Mansfield
    - Providencia, Ravine Tunnel, old #532, 17x24 60 (Folder 46-12)
    - Moerlein Tunnel, Enriquita, Frederick Tunnel, old #537, 12.5x18 40 (Folder 46-13)
    - Enriquita works, lower levels with proposed raise, color, old #538, 1962; 16x23.5 80 (Folder 46-14)
    - Enriquita works, vertical section, old #539, 1962; 8.5x11 200 (Folder 46-15)
    - Providence-Enriquita, photocopy of original?, old #544B, 1935; 7.25x14 200 (Folder 47-1)
    - Providencia, Jack Escover, Yellow Kid, Jr., old #544E1, 1961; 8.5x11 40 (Folder 47-2)
    - Providencia, general workings, old #544E2, 1966; 8.5x11 40 (Folder 47-3)
    - Enriquita, Moerlein drift and connection to old Main Tunnel, pencil, color, old #544G, 1964; 8.5x11 40 (Folder 47-4)
    - Enriquita, Moerlein drift and connection to old Main Tunnel, pencil, color, old #544H, 1964; 8.5x11 40 (Folder 47-5)
    - Providencia Tunnel, Escover works, old #544I, 13x18 20 (Folder 47-6)
    - Providencia Tunnel, old works, 1864 copy from Charley, old #544I2, 15x18 20 (Folder 47-7)
    - Enriquita, Moerlein drifts, contour map of Providencia on verso, old #544K, 1965; 17x24 200 (Folder 47-8)
    - Providencia, elevations from Engine Flat (Enriquita), old #544M, 18x23 40 (Folder 47-9)
      Frederick?
    - Providencia, elevations from Engine Flat (Enriquita), old #544M, 15x17 40 (Folder 47-10)
    - Providencia, black, old #544M2, 15x17 40 (Folder 47-11)
    - Enriquita, rough sketch Eldredge tunnel, old #544O, 18x24 40 (Folder 47-12)
    - Providence-Enriquita photocopy (see 544B), different scale, negative and blueprint, old #544Q, 1935; 8.5x17 170 (Folder 47-13)
    - Providencia, recent work from Escover shaft, old #544V, 1966; 18x35 8 (Folder 47-14)
      Ross, Kirk
    - Enriquita Mine, color, old #526A, 28.5x43 10 (Folder 47-15)
    - Shaft map, Enriquita Dump, 18x24 20 (Folder 48-1)
    - Main shaft, tunnel plan, color, 22x33 (Folder 48-2)
    - Enriquita Villiage after Louis Janin, plastic, 9.5x12 (Folder 48-3)
  - SAN ANTONIO, GUADALUPE, OUTSIDE MINES
    - San Antonio, surface geology, upper crosscut, old #554, 1962; 11.5x18 40 (Folder 48-4)
      Herring, Schneider
    - Guadalupe furnaces, 1 and 4, old #651, 1879; 19x22 6 (Folder 48-5)
      Healy, Von Leicht
    - Guadalupe Mine, 1875/1880; 24x29.5 20 (Folder 48-6)
      Healy
    - Guadalupe, Portland Cement Co., Confidence Gold Mine Mill, old #602, 1926?; 22.5x78 (Folder 48-7)
    - General plan of gold mill, blueprint, old #652, 1917; 25.5x33 4 (Folder 48-8)
      Herbert Haas
    - General plan of gold mill, blueprint, old #652, 1917; 25.5x33 4 (Folder 48-9)
    - Ella Copper Co. (Marg.), Cannon & San Vicinte, old #331, 1902; 17x23 10 ch (Folder 48-10)
    - Ella Copper Co. (Marg.), Cannon & San Vicinte, old #337, 1902; 20x21 20 ch (Folder 48-11)
      Carson
    - Idria Mine, Austria, Tafel I, old #328, 1880; 17x22 (Folder 48-12)
      Plaminek, Waldheim
    - Northwest Mine, old #332, 22x35 20 (Folder 48-13)
      Reade, Darby
    - Strawberry Mine, surface geology, 1962; 24x31 40 (Folder 48-14)
      Linn, Rockwell
    - Strawberry Mine, surface geology, 1962; 24x31 40 (Folder 48-15)
    - Strawberry Mine, Tungsten, surface geology, 1962; 24x31 40 (Folder 49-1)
    - Plan of the hoisting works of the Guadalupe Quicksilver Mine., 1879; 18 x 18.75 20 (Folder 49-2)
      Von Leicht, Healey
    - Map of the Guadalupe mine in Santa Clara County, pieces of map taped together, 20 (Folder 49-3)
      Charles T. Healey
  - SAN MATEO
    - General Map, #1, #2, 1938 adits, 520-530, blueprint of 569N, old #563, 1964; 17x22 40 (Folder 49-4)
    - San Mateo, composite long projection, vertical cross section along E-F, old #566, 1964; 8.75x24 40 (Folder 49-5)
    - San Mateo, composite, vertical cross section along C-D, old #567, 1964; 8.75x18 40 (Folder 49-6)
    - San Mateo, new works, to overlay, old #569B, 1966; 8.5x11 40 (Folder 49-7)
    - San Mateo, 135 level, 1924, old 569C, 11x15 (Folder 49-8)
    - San Mateo, modern work, to overlay map by Frederick, old #569E, 1966; 8.5x11 40 (Folder 49-9)
    - San Mateo, cross section C-D, see 567, old #569F, 1961; 8.5x18 40 (Folder 49-10)
    - San Mateo, cross section A-B, see 568, old #569G, 1964; 8.5 x 18.5 40 (Folder 49-11)
    - Plan 1924 shaft (125) and Derby creek Tunnel, old #569H, 12x17.5 40 (Folder 49-12)
      Ingle?
    - San Mateo, composite vertical cross section E-F, old 569I, 1964; 19x22 40 (Folder 49-13)
    - San Mateo, composite vertical cross section E-F, old 569I, 1964; 8.75x25 40 (Folder 49-14)
    - Plan 1924 shaft and Derby Creek Tunnel #1, same as 569H, old #569K, 1964; 11x12 40 (Folder 49-15)
    - San Mateo, horizontal, #1 Moerlein works, old #569M, 1964; 13x17 50 (Folder 50-1)
    - Old works, Schneider crosscut, #1, #2, 1935, 520-530, old #569N, 1964; 17x22 40 (Folder 50-2)
    - San Mateo, composite from book 46 (1900)surveys, old #5690, 1964; 21x31 40 (Folder 50-3)
    - San Mateo, horizontal and vertical profile, old #569P, 1874; 18x20 20 (Folder 50-4)
  - SENATOR
    - Plan of the Senator mine, surface 500, old #570, 1916; 27x53.5 50 (Folder 50-5)
      Webber
    - Senator workings, 125-1300, with Guadalupe property line, old #571, 1935; 29x40 50 (Folder 50-6)
    - Senator workings under Landers, Juessen, 1909-19,model made from this, old #585, 1919; 20.5 x 22.5 50 (Folder 50-7)
    - Senator workings under Landers, reverse print, 1919; 20.5 x 22.5 50 (Folder 50-8)
    - Senator?, 300 level, old #586, 9x11 (Folder 50-9)
    - Senator?, 125 level, old #587, 10x22 (Folder 50-10)
    - Senator?, 400-500, old #588, 15.5 x 15.5 (Folder 50-11)
    - Senator?, 500-600, old #589, 14x15.5 (Folder 50-12)
    - Senator?, 500-600, old #589, 10.75 x 11.75 (Folder 50-13)
    - Senator?, 600 to start 800, old #590, 13x18 (Folder 50-14)
    - Senator?, 125-800, old #591, 26.5x28 (Folder 50-15)
    - Senator?, 125-800, old #591, 27.5x30 (Folder 51-1)
    - Senator?, 800-1000, old #592, 18x21 (Folder 51-2)
    - Senator?, 300-500, vertical and horizontal, old #594, 27.5x30 (Folder 51-3)
    - Senator?, 550-700, #2 vein stope section, vertical, old #595, 17x22 (Folder 51-4)
    - Vein #2, logitudinal section in in plane of shaft, 260-900, start 1000, old #596, 19x22 50 (Folder 51-5)
    - Vein #3, hanging wall vein, longitudinal section of plane in shaft, old #597, 22x22 50 (Folder 51-6)
      CNS?
    - Projection on vertical plane, N50°W, surface-1200, old #598, 31x32 (Folder 51-7)
    - Vertical section sketch map with second exits for fire, 260-1000, blueprint, old #599, 26x32 50 (Folder 51-8)
      Webber?
    - Senator workings, 125-1300, see 571, color, 1935; 29x40 50 (Folder 51-9)
    - Elevation of the Senator Mine, vertical cross section, old #573, 1916; 23x66 50 (Folder 51-10)
    - Senator Mine, Map and Model of principal workings showing location of all known ore bodies, color, 1919; 19.5x24 50 (Folder 51-11)
      E.J., Jr.
    - Senator mine, in part, color, 1917; 11.5 x 17.5 50 (Folder 51-12)
    - Hacienda and Senator Mines, 1918; 20.5 x 26.5 50 (Folder 51-13)
      O.Tinnemann
  - GENERAL, NEW ALMADEN
    - New Almaden Underground Workings, General, Santa Rita, Theatre, Randol, old #10, 1880; 25x41 80 (Folder 51-14)
    - Profile and plan of Randol, Isabel, Main, New World, Day, old #262, 22x26 200 (Folder 51=15)
    - Main Tunnel Workings, old #100, 1878; 42x58 20 (Folder 52-1)
    - Main Tunnel Workings, reduction, 1878; 12.5x30 50 (Folder 52-2)
    - Main Tunnel Workings, reduction, 1878; 12.5x30 50 (Folder 52-3)
    - New Almaden Mine Levels, old #101A., ca. 1860; 25.5x35 (Folder 52-4)
    - New Almaden Mine Levels, old #101B., ca. 1860; 25.5x35 (Folder 52-5)
    - Mine Hill, apex to furnaces, profile of various tunnels, Plate 13, original, old #103, 1875; 22x34 100 (Folder 52-6)
    - Mine Hill, Santa Rita, San Francisco, Almaden, old #112, 30x41.5 40 (Folder 52-7)
    - Mine Hill, San Francisco, blueprint, old #188, 1882; 25x39 80 (Folder 52-8)
    - Mine Hill, reduction of Bailey plate, old #190A, 1954?; 8x10 (Folder 52-9)
      Bailey
    - Valasco to San Francisco, vertical section, old #230, 1880; 26x37.5 80 (Folder 52-10)
    - Photo of Mine Office map on roller section, old #234, 7x14 (Folder 52-11)
    - New Almaden Mine plan, color, old #235A, 1885; 18.5x30 150 (Folder 52-12)
    - Randol, San Francisco, partial, old #236, 14x27 (Folder 52-13)
    - New Almaden Mine plan, copy of 235A [13-20], old #237., 1885; 18.5x30 150 (Folder 52-14)
    - New Almaden Mine plan, Diamond hole drill #7, vertical section, old #219L, 10x16.5 (Folder 52-15)
    - New Almaden Mine plan, Diamond hole drill #7, vertical section, old 219C, 10x16.5 (Folder 53-1)
    - New Almaden Mine plan, Diamond hole drill #7, vertical section, old 219C, 10x16.5 (Folder 53-2)
    - Healey glass model sections, 25 paper sections, 7 paper sections of New World, old #325, 1874; 8x21.5 100 (Folder 53-3)